[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What factor is the reason for economists to believe that countries are gradually becoming more economically interdependent?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["There are many multinational corporations that design, manufacture, and sell products around the world.", "Global trade is largely aided by the constant progress of technologies.", "Financial markets in many countries have been opened to participants from foreign countries."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the protagonist role of Jim Halsey in the 1986 thriller The Hitcher?", "correct_answer": "C. Thomas Howell", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlie Sheen", "Rob Lowe", "Emilio Estevez"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tea is made by a process called infusing.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of unique activity is characteristic of the African Pygmy Mouse, the smallest rodent in the world?", "correct_answer": "It piles up pebbles in front of its burrow.", "incorrect_answers": ["It sings at night.", "It disguises its young using leaves.", "It starts dancing when it feels threatened by a predator."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what stage of the development of the fetus do eyelashes form?", "correct_answer": "Between the 7th and 8th week", "incorrect_answers": ["Around the 26th week", "Between the 13th and 14th week", "Around the 20th week"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Michael Myers finally kills his other sister in the movie Halloween: Resurrection.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As of the beginning of the new millennium, this was  the approximate number of Americans who receive a massage annually.", "correct_answer": "20,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["15,000", "150,000", "3,000,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What maximum height at the withers can Chihuahuas reach?", "correct_answer": "15 inches (38 cm)", "incorrect_answers": ["24 inches (60 cm)", "12 inches (30 cm)", "9 inches (22 cm)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Copper?", "correct_answer": "Cu", "incorrect_answers": ["Cp", "Co", "C"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Bachs reason in writing the Etudes?", "correct_answer": "Keep his children occupied", "incorrect_answers": ["Earn money  - they were sold as study  pieces", "Show that the harpsichord was inferior to the piano", "Show that he could compose easy pieces, thereby promoting a large number of students to his study"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do Troy and Gabriella go to prom together in High School Musical 3?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which square is not correctly matched with the capital city in which it is located?", "correct_answer": "Azadi Square - Karachi", "incorrect_answers": ["Red Square - Moscow", "Senate Square - Helsinki", "Leicester Square - London"]}]